<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- cobra / speed tattoos -->

  <I_EMSpeedSma.label>Tattoo kit (cobra - small)</I_EMSpeedSma.label>
  <I_EMSpeedSma.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a cobra, there is enough here for a small tattoo on a hand or foot. This design increases speed a little. May make eating a time-consuming process.</I_EMSpeedSma.description>

  <I_EMSpeedMed.label>Tattoo kit (cobra - medium)</I_EMSpeedMed.label>
  <I_EMSpeedMed.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a cobra, there is enough here for a sizeable tattoo on an arm or leg. This design increases speed by a modest amount. May make eating a time-consuming process.</I_EMSpeedMed.description>

  <I_EMSpeedBig.label>Tattoo kit (cobra - large)</I_EMSpeedBig.label>
  <I_EMSpeedBig.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a cobra, there is enough here for a large tattoo on someones chest or back. This design increases speed by a sizeable amount. May make eating a time-consuming process.</I_EMSpeedBig.description>


  <!-- thrumbo / pain tattoos -->

  <I_EMPainSma.label>Tattoo kit (thrumbo - small)</I_EMPainSma.label>
  <I_EMPainSma.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a thrumbo, there is enough here for a small tattoo on a hand or foot. This design decreases pain a little. Will make you a little more susceptible to the elements.</I_EMPainSma.description>

  <I_EMPainMed.label>Tattoo kit (thrumbo - medium)</I_EMPainMed.label>
  <I_EMPainMed.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a thrumbo, there is enough here for a sizeable tattoo on an arm or leg. This design decreases pain by a modest amount. Will make you a little more susceptible to the elements.</I_EMPainMed.description>

  <I_EMPainBig.label>Tattoo kit (thrumbo - large)</I_EMPainBig.label>
  <I_EMPainBig.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a thrumbo, there is enough here for a large tattoo on someones chest or back. This design decreases pain by a sizeable amount. Will make you a little more susceptible to the elements.</I_EMPainBig.description>


  <!-- monkey / manipulation tattoos -->

  <I_EMManipSma.label>Tattoo kit (monkey - small)</I_EMManipSma.label>
  <I_EMManipSma.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a monkey, there is enough here for a small tattoo on a hand or foot. This design increases manipulation a little. Psychic phenomena are a little more effective too.</I_EMManipSma.description>

  <I_EMManipMed.label>Tattoo kit (monkey - medium)</I_EMManipMed.label>
  <I_EMManipMed.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a monkey, there is enough here for a sizeable tattoo on an arm or leg. This design increases manipulation by a modest amount. Psychic phenomena are a little more effective too.</I_EMManipMed.description>

  <I_EMManipBig.label>Tattoo kit (monkey - large)</I_EMManipBig.label>
  <I_EMManipBig.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a monkey, there is enough here for a large tattoo on someones chest or back. This design increases manipulation by a sizeable amount. Psychic phenomena are a little more effective too.</I_EMManipBig.description>


  <!-- mechanoid / consciousness tattoos -->

  <I_EMConSma.label>Tattoo kit (mechanoid - small)</I_EMConSma.label>
  <I_EMConSma.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a mechanoid, there is enough here for a small tattoo on a hand or foot. This design increases consciousness a little, it is also scary for others to look at.</I_EMConSma.description>

  <I_EMConMed.label>Tattoo kit (mechanoid - medium)</I_EMConMed.label>
  <I_EMConMed.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a mechanoid, there is enough here for a sizeable tattoo on an arm or leg. This design increases consciousness by a modest amount, it is also scary for others to look at.</I_EMConMed.description>

  <I_EMConBig.label>Tattoo kit (mechanoid - large)</I_EMConBig.label>
  <I_EMConBig.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a mechanoid, there is enough here for a large tattoo on someones chest or back. This design increases consciousness by a sizeable amount, it is also scary for others to look at.</I_EMConBig.description>


  <!-- muffalo / mental break tattoos -->

  <I_EMBreakSma.label>Tattoo kit (muffalo - small)</I_EMBreakSma.label>
  <I_EMBreakSma.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a cobra, there is enough here for a small tattoo on a hand or foot. This design increases mental break threshold a little. Makes movement a little slower.</I_EMBreakSma.description>

  <I_EMBreakMed.label>Tattoo kit (muffalo - medium)</I_EMBreakMed.label>
  <I_EMBreakMed.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a muffalo, there is enough here for a sizeable tattoo on an arm or leg. This design increases mental break threshold  by a modest amount. Makes movement a little slower.</I_EMBreakMed.description>

  <I_EMBreakBig.label>Tattoo kit (muffalo - large)</I_EMBreakBig.label>
  <I_EMBreakBig.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a muffalo, there is enough here for a large tattoo on someones chest or back. This design increases mental break threshold by a sizeable amount. Makes movement a little slower.</I_EMBreakBig.description>


  <!-- insectoid / mental break tattoos -->

  <I_EMBloodSma.label>Tattoo kit (insectoid - small)</I_EMBloodSma.label>
  <I_EMBloodSma.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of an insectoid, there is enough here for a small tattoo on a hand or foot. This design increases blood pumping a little. It will also reduce learning speed a little.</I_EMBloodSma.description>

  <I_EMBloodMed.label>Tattoo kit (insectoid - medium)</I_EMBloodMed.label>
  <I_EMBloodMed.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of an insectoid, there is enough here for a sizeable tattoo on an arm or leg. This design increases blood pumping by a modest amount. It will also reduce learning speed a little.</I_EMBloodMed.description>

  <I_EMBloodBig.label>Tattoo kit (insectoid - large)</I_EMBloodBig.label>
  <I_EMBloodBig.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of an insectoid, there is enough here for a large tattoo on someones chest or back. This design increases blood pumping by a sizeable amount. It will also reduce learning speed a little.</I_EMBloodBig.description>


  <!-- rose / melee tattoos -->

  <I_EMMeleeSma.label>Tattoo kit (rose - small)</I_EMMeleeSma.label>
  <I_EMMeleeSma.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a rose, there is enough here for a small tattoo on a hand or foot. This design increases melee ability a little. It will also reduce pain threshold a little.</I_EMMeleeSma.description>

  <I_EMMeleeMed.label>Tattoo kit (rose - medium)</I_EMMeleeMed.label>
  <I_EMMeleeMed.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a rose, there is enough here for a sizeable tattoo on an arm or leg. This design increases melee ability by a modest amount. It will also reduce pain threshold a little.</I_EMMeleeMed.description>

  <I_EMMeleeBig.label>Tattoo kit (rose - large)</I_EMMeleeBig.label>
  <I_EMMeleeBig.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a rose, there is enough here for a large tattoo on someones chest or back. This design increases melee ability by a sizeable amount. It will also reduce pain threshold a little.</I_EMMeleeBig.description>


  <!-- sun / shooting tattoos -->

  <I_EMShootSma.label>Tattoo kit (sun - small)</I_EMShootSma.label>
  <I_EMShootSma.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a sun, there is enough here for a small tattoo on a hand or foot. This design increases shooting ability a little. It will also reduce work speed a little.</I_EMShootSma.description>

  <I_EMShootMed.label>Tattoo kit (sun - medium)</I_EMShootMed.label>
  <I_EMShootMed.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a sun, there is enough here for a sizeable tattoo on an arm or leg. This design increases shooting ability by a modest amount. It will also reduce work speed a little.</I_EMShootMed.description>

  <I_EMShootBig.label>Tattoo kit (sun - large)</I_EMShootBig.label>
  <I_EMShootBig.description>A set of carefully prepared inks and templates used to tattoo the design of a sun, there is enough here for a large tattoo on someones chest or back. This design increases shooting ability by a sizeable amount. It will also reduce work speed a little.</I_EMShootBig.description>


</LanguageData>